[{"answer": " Need some advice, huh", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Don't worry about the that place, they're just a bunch of moralistic bus", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I got suspended when I was young, too. I was pretty cocky in my day", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "100 years!", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who gave it to you", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " my friend. Who's my friend to you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Buzz my friend never helps anybody but himself", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He's no father to you", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What the fuck is this", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It looks like dwarf bowling", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend, you ever do the 'Swing'", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Not while I'm in training", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " No. Do You", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, that was plan A", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Plan B is your dad", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, please", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " What's plan C", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Come on my friend, what about plan C", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Plan C...  ...is me", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I have someone for you to play with my friend", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I have someone for you to play Blueface with my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " my friend, I want you to get out of this town", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Did that porcupine say he'd get you back on the tour", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I'm getting to like it here", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I gotta survive", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " You're just like you mother! Always jealous", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "She ran away to be with that...  that Motocross champion", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Who's there", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Junior who", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Too late for what, my friend", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You got any broken bones", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You shouldn't touch her", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Nobody touches her. Except me. I touch her. my friend told me you played bounc", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " What did you do to Buzz", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " I don't want to play", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You're really pissing me off", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "My word is good, and it'll always be good. When did I ever give my word to you", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "My word is good, and it'll always be good. When did I ever give my word to you", "docId": "Spare-Me.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Fuck plan C", "qsentId": 40}]